{
    "subject": "resource/Don't_Raise_the_Bridge,_Lower_the_River",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Bernard_Cribbins",
    "human_readable": "The movie 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River' stars Bernard Cribbins.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9730601906776428,
            "question": "What role does Bernard Cribbins play in 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9602416753768921,
            "question": "Who stars in the movie 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7395299673080444,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie starring Bernard Cribbins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6636456251144409,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a movie starring Bernard Cribbins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6632829308509827,
            "question": "Name a movie featuring Bernard Cribbins."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.660098135471344,
            "question": "Has Bernard Cribbins starred in any films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6095226407051086,
            "question": "Is Bernard Cribbins an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5938755869865417,
            "question": "What other movies has Bernard Cribbins been in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.486357182264328,
            "question": "Is Bernard Cribbins a well-known actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3536756634712219,
            "question": "Bernard Cribbins is known for what type of roles?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The movie 'Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River' stars Bernard Cribbins.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3652_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Bernard Cribbins a well-known actor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3652_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other movies has Bernard Cribbins been in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3652_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Bernard Cribbins an actor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3652_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3652_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3652_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3652_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3652_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3652_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3652_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3652_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3652_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3652_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3652_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information clearly states that \"Don\u2019t Raise the Bridge, Lower the River\" co-stars Bernard Cribbins, supporting the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}